In this video, I'm going to show you the commit history with "git log".
Neste vdeo, mostrarei o histrico de commits com "git log".
I'm currently in my terminal, within the "demo" Git repository.
Eu estou atualmente no meu terminal, dentro do repositrio Git "demo".
Since we just performed a commit, we have a clean working directory;
Como acabamos de realizar um commit, temos um diretrio de trabalho limpo; ento
so there's nothing else to commit.
no h mais nada para cometer.
To prove to you that all our changes that we just recently made are in the Git repository,
Para provar a voc que todas as nossas mudanas que acabamos de fazer esto no repositrio
we can use Git's log command to show our listing of commits.
Git, podemos usar o comando log do Git para mostrar nossa lista de commits.
If I simply type "git log", then press enter,
Se eu simplesmente digitar "git log", ento pressione enter,
Git responds with all the commits that are part of this repository.
o Git responde com todos os commits que fazem parte deste repositrio.
Incidentally, there's only one commit; let's go through it.
Alis, h apenas um commit; vamos passar por isso.
It starts off with the commit id. So we have "commit"; space; and then this long identifier:
Comea com o ID de confirmao. Ento ns temos "commit"; espao; e, em seguida, esse identificador
that's the SHA-1 identifier that's used to uniquely identify commits within a repository.
longo: esse  o identificador SHA-1 usado para identificar com exclusividade os commits em um repositrio.
After the commit id, we have the author, which happens to be me,
Aps o ID de commit, temos o autor, que  eu, seguido
followed by the date, then our commit message.
da data e depois da mensagem de commit.
In this case, we had our multi-line commit message that we entered using our core editor.
Nesse caso, tivemos nossa mensagem de confirmao de vrias linhas que inserimos usando nosso editor principal.
We can get similar information by using the "show" command.
Podemos obter informaes semelhantes usando o comando "show".
Just type "git show", and it will show the last commit and a diff containing all the changes.
Basta digitar "git show", e ele mostrar o ltimo commit e um diff contendo todas as alteraes.
To get out of the show command, press 'q'.
Para sair do comando show, pressione 'q'.